allvitalpoints.com 2014-10-09

# Privacy policy

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our website, subscribe to our articles, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our website anonymously.

Google as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google’s use of any cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our website and other websites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the any cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience, to improve our website, or to improve our reader experience.

 **Do we use cookies?**  
No. We may use cookies in future to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites.

 **Personal data protection compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with what is appropriate personal data protection. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Protection of children**  
We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at:

http://www.allvitalpoints.com/terms-conditions/

 **If you need to contact us, please send email to:**

 **angela.taylor@allvitalpoints.com**

Category:  Product #: Regular price:$ (Sale ends !) Available from: Condition:  Good  ! Order now!

Reviewed by  on. Rating:
